Guide To the University Of California, Santa Cruz Contemporary Classical Collection ARS.0103
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Unusual Items, 92 audiotape reel(s)
  - Stravinsky; Aschaffenburg; Smith; Lewin; Viller; Klein; Harrison; Boone; Pfitzner, circa 1957-1967; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 2, Reel 199)
    Aschaffenburg, Walter, 1927-2005. Three dances (1966-67). Cleveland Orchestra. James Levine, conductor.
    Smith, Russell, 1927-1998. Piano concerto no. 2. World premiere. Joela Jones, piano. Cleveland Orchestra. George Szell, conductor.
    Lewin, David, 1933-2003. Fantasy adagio, for violin and orchestra. Daniel [indicipherable], violinist. Michael Cherry, conductor.
    Miller, Edward J. (Edward Jay), 1930-2013. Orchestral changes. Louis Lane, conductor.
    Klein, Lothar, 1932-3004. Musique a go-go. Louis Lane, conductor.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Seven pastorales. Premiere. Oakland Chamber Orchestra. Gerhard Samuel, conductor.
    Boone, Charles, 1939-. Starfish. Oakland Chamber Orchestra. Gerhard Samuel, conductor.
    Pfitzner, Hans, 1869-1949. Violin concerto. Max Strub, violin. Westfalian Symphony Orchestra. Hubert Reitter, conductor.
    Aschaffenburg, Walter, 1927-2005; Smith, Russell, 1927-1998; Lewin, David, 1933-2003; Miller, Edward J (Edward Jay), 1930-2013; Klein, Lothar; Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003; Boone, Charles; Pfitzner, Hans, 1869-1949; Cleveland Orchestra; Oakland Chamber Orchestra; Westfälisches Sinfonie-Orchester; Levine, James; Szell, George; Cherry, Michael; Lane, Louis; Samuel, Gerhard; Reitter, Hubert; Jones, Joela; Strub, Max, 1900-1966
  - Couperin; Frescobaldi; KPFA broadcast, circa 1967; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 2, Reel 201)
    Couperin, [unspecified]. unidentified works. Charles Koenig, harpsichord.
    Frescobaldi, Girolamo, 1583-1643. unidentified works. Charles Koenig, harpsichord.
    [indicipherable]. KPFA. October 13, 1967.
    Koenig, Charles, 1923-; Frescobaldi, Girolamo, 1583-1643
  - Bach; Subotnick; Harrison, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 2, Reel 202)
    Bach, [unspecified]. Violin sonata.
    Subotnick, Morton, 1933-. unidentified work.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Labyrinth no. 3.
    Subotnick, Morton; Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003
  - Corrêa de Araujo; Carvalho; Pasquini; Scarlatti; Viola; Bach; Frobengen; Cabanilles, circa 1966; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 205)
    Corrêa de Araujo, Francisco, 1584-1654. Tiento. Geraint Jones, organ. Coimbra University. July 2, 1966.
    Carvalho, João de Sousa, 1745-. Allegro. Geraint Jones, organ. Coimbra University. July 2, 1966.
    Pasquini, Bernardo, 1637-1710. Partita on 'la folia'. Geraint Jones, organ. Coimbra University. July 2, 1966.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, organ, K. 287, D major. Geraint Jones, organ. Church of São Vicente de Fora, Lisbon.
    Viola, Anselm, 1738-1798. Sonatina. Geraint Jones, organ. Church of São Vicente de Fora, Lisbon.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, organ, K. 288, D major. Geraint Jones, organ. Church of São Vicente de Fora, Lisbon.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Jesus, meine Zuversicht (Chorale prelude). Geraint Jones, organ. Girona, Spain.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Fugue. Geraint Jones, organ. Girona, Spain.
    Corrêa de Araujo, Francisco, 1584-1654. Tiento. Geraint Jones, organ. [Mafra?], Spain.
    Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667. Canzona in F. Geraint Jones, organ. [Mafra?], Spain.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Chorale preludes, BWV 672, 673, 674. Geraint Jones, organ. Solsona, Spain.
    Cabanilles, Juan, 1644-1712. Tiento. Geraint Jones, organ. Solsona, Spain.
    Carvalho, João de Sousa, 1745-; Corrêa de Araujo, Francisco; Pasquini, Bernardo, 1637-1710; Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757; Viola, Anselm, 1738-1798; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667; Cabanilles, Juan, 1644-1712; Jones, Geraint, 1917-1998
  - Cage: Sonatas and interludes for prepared piano; Paderewski plays., circa 1965; 1 Linear Feet [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 206)
    Cage, John, 1912-1992. Sonatas and interludes for prepared piano. LP dubbing. Maro Ajemian, prepared piano. 1965
    Padereweski plays.
    Cage, John; Ajemian, Maro
  - Takemitsu; Mamiya; Hayashi; Baird; Matsushita, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 207)
    Takemitsu, Tōru, 1930-1996. Sky, horse, death.
    Mamiya, Michio, 1929-. Composition for mixed chorus.
    Hayashi, Hikaru, 1931-2012. Cantata 'some views of atomic bombing'.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Expressions, for violin and orchestra.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Chamber composition for eight.
    Takemitsu, Tōru; Mamiya, Michio, 1929-; Hayashi, Hikaru, 1931-2012; Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981; Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990
  - Japanese classical music, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 208)
    Japanese classical music. Japanese radio.
  - Morthenson; Karkoff; Bark; Hambraeus; Blomdahl; Sigurbjornsson; Melinas; Fongaard; Pergament; Claude Stevenson discusses Blomdahl, circa 1966-1968; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 209)
    Morthenson, Jan, 1940-. Neutron Star. 1967.
    Karkoff, Maurice, 1927-2013. Landschaft aus Schreien, op. 86. Sven Erik Back, conductor. December 17 and 20, 1967.
    Bark, Jan, 1934-. Bar, for electronically manipulated and unmanipulated regular instruments. All played by the composer.
    Hambraeus, Bengt, 1928-2000. Fresques sonores. 1967.
    Hambraeus, Bengt, 1928-2000. Transfoguration. LP mono dubbing.
    Blomdahl, Karl-Birger, 1916-1968. Altisonance. LP mono dubbing.
    Sigurbjornsson, Thorkel, 1938-2013. String quartet. LP mono dubbing.
    Melinas, Arne, 1933-2002. Intensity. 1966.
    Fongaard, Bjorn, 1919-1980. Homo sapiens. 1966.
    Pergament, Moses, 1893-1977. Four poems, for soprano and orchestra. LP mono dubbing.
    Claude Stevenson discusses Blomdahl's musical progress up to his opera 'Aniara'. Includes musical excerpts.
    Morthenson, Jan W, 1940-; Karkoff, Maurice; Bäck, Sven-Erik; Bark, Jan; Hambræus, Bengt, 1928-2000; Blomdahl, Karl-Birger, 1916-1968; Þorkell Sigurbjörnsson, 1938-2013; Fongaard, Bjørn, 1919-1980; Pergament, Moses, 1893-1977
  - Miyoshi: Ondine, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 210)
    Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013. Ondine.
    Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013
  - Foss: Phorion; Jacob: Trio for clarinet, viola, and piano; Mahler: Des Knaben Wunderhorn, circa 1969; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 211)
    Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009. Phorion, after Bach's E major prelude for violin [i.e. Baroque variations. On a Bach prelude]. Los Angeles Philharmonic. Conducted by the composer.
    Jacob, Gordon, 1895-1984. Trio for clarinet, viola, and piano. Pacifica Chamber Players (Tom Ross, Carol Garrett, Julian White). 1969.
    Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Des Knaben Wunderhorn. Josephine Veasey, mezzo-soprano. John Shirley-Quirk, baritone. Los Angeles Philharmonic. Zubin Mehta, conductor.
    Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009; Jacob, Gordon, 1895-1984; Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911; Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra; Pacifica Chamber Players; Veasey, Josephine; Shirley-Quirk, John; Mehta, Zubin
  - Merikanto; Wiren; Lilburn; Martinu; Dvorak; Bird; Nono; Hartmann; Giseler; Milhaud; Mamiya; Penderecki; Gorecki; Berlioz; Bialas; Mieg; Scriabin, circa 1968; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 212)
    Merikanto, Aarre, 1893-1958. Concerto for violin, clarinet, horn and strings. Finnish Radio Orchestra. Conducted by composer.
    Wirén, Dag, 1905-1986. String quartet no. 4. Kundel Quartet.
    Lilburn, Douglas, 1915-2001. Nine short pieces (1965-66). Margaret Nielsen, piano. KPFA. November, 1968.
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959. Sextet for strings. Sestetto Chigiano. January 6, 1968.
    Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Sextet in A. Sestetto Chigiano. January 6, 1968.
    Bird, Joseph. Water music. Max Keuhaus, percussion.
    Nono, Luigi, 1924-1990. Canto sospeso.
    Hartmann, Karl Amadeus, 1905-1963. Gesangsszene. Dietrich Fischer-Dieskau, baritone. Cologne Radio Symphony Orchestra. Joseph Keilberth, conductor
    Giseler, Walter. Concerto for string orchestra. Southwest German Chamber Orchestra. Friedrich Tilegant, conductor.
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Quartet no. 13. Parrenin Quartet.
    Mamiya, Michio, ǂd 1929-. Enburi. Japanese Symphony Orchestra. Hiroyuki Iwaki, conductor.
    Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-. Dies irae. Woytowicz, soprano. Ochman, tenor. Ladysz, bass. Cracow Philharmonic Chorus and Orchestra. Henryk Czyz, conductor.
    Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-. Polymorphia.
    Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-. De natura sonoris.
    Górecki, Henryk Mikołaj, 1933-2010. Genesis II. Polish radio.
    Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869. Damnation de Faust, Ballet des sylphes. Wanda Landowska, piano. Recorded from Welte piano roll.
    Bialas, Günter, 1907-1995. Concerto lirico. Christoph Eschenbach, piano. Cologne Radio Orchestra. Hans Martin Schneidt, conductor.
    Mieg, Peter, 1906-1990. Toccata, arioso and gigue. Southwest German Chorus and Orchestra. Thomas Ungar, conductor.
    Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Etudes, piano, op. 8. Sviatoslav Richter, piano.
    Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Sonatas, piano, no. 6, op. 62. Sviatoslav Richter, piano.
    Merikanto, Aarre, 1893-1958; Radion sinfoniaorkesteri; Wirén, Dag, 1905-1986; Lilburn, Douglas, 1915-2001; Nielsen, Margaret; Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959; Sestetto Chigiano; Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904; Nono, Luigi; Hartmann, Karl Amadeus, 1905-1963; Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-2012; Kölner Rundfunk-Sinfonie-Orchester; Keilberth, Joseph; Südwestdeutsches Kammerorchester Pforzheim; Tilegant, Friedrich, 1910-1968; Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974.; Quatuor Parrenin; Mamiya, Michio, 1929-; NHK Kōkyō Gakudan; Iwaki, Hiroyuki; Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-; Filharmonia Krakowska; Filharmonia Krakowska. Chór; Czyż, Henryk, 1923-2003; Górecki, Henryk Mikołaj, 1933-2010; Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869; Landowska, Wanda; Bialas, Günter, 1907-1995; Eschenbach, Christoph; Schneidt, Hanns-Martin; Mieg, Peter; Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany). Chœur; Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany). Orchester; Ungar, Thomas, 1931-; Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915; Richter, Sviatoslav, 1915-1997
  - Harrison: Labyrinth no. 3, Concerto for violin with percussion orchestra, 2 pieces for psaltery, circa 1967-1968; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 213)
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Labrynth no. 3. 4 of the projected 9 movements. Conducted by Gerhard Samuel. Cabrillo Festival. 1967.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Concertos, violin, percussion ensemble. Austin Reller, violin. Percussionists named on tape by Charles Shore. Cabrillo Festival. 1968.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. 2 pieces for psaltery. Played by the composer. undated.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003; Samuel, Gerhard; Reller, Austin; Cabrillo Music Festival
  - Harrison; Glasmo; Brant; Kobialka, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 214)
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Concerto in slendro.
    [Glasmo?], Glenn. Raga.
    Brant, Henry, ǂd 1913-2008. Hieroglyphic for violin.
    Kobialka, Daniel. [Untitled] work for tape. World premiere.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003; Brant, Henry, 1913-2008; Kobialka, Daniel
  - Haydn: Symphony no. 104. Beecham rehearsal, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 215)
    Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Symphonies, H. I, 104, D major. Beecham rehearsal.
    Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961
  - Starer: Symphony no. 3; Lees: Concerto for string quartet and symphony orchestra; Martin: Piano concero no. 2, 1970-1972; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 216)
    Starer, Robert. Symphonies, no. 3. Boston Symphony Orchestra. William Steinberg, conductor. Winter, 1971-1972.
    Lees, Benjamin, 1924-2010. Concertos, violins (2), viola, cello, orchestra. Boston Symphony Orchestra. William Steinberg, conductor. Winter, 1971-1972.
    Martin, Frank, 1890-1974. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 2. Paul Badura-Skoda, piano. Philadelphia Orchestra. Thomas Schippers, conductor. 1970.
    Starer, Robert; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Steinberg, William; Lees, Benjamin, 1924-2010; Martin, Frank, 1890-1974; Badura-Skoda, Paul; Philadelphia Orchestra; Schippers, Thomas
  - Bergman; Segerstam; Meriläinen; Rydman; Salmenhaara, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 217)
    Bergman, Erik, 1911-2006. [untitled].
    Segerstam, Leif. [untitled].
    Meriläinen, Usko. [untitled].
    Rydman, Kari. [untitled].
    Salmenhaara, Erik. [untitled].
    Bergman, Erik, 1911-2006; Segerstam, Leif; Meriläinen, Usko; Rydman, Kari; Salmenhaara, Erik
  - Poser; Bresgen; Marx; Rosenthal; Maderna; Nono; Palmer; Bartok, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 218)
    Poser, Hans, 1917-1970. Kassel music days.
    Bresgen, Cesar, 1913-1988. Sonatina in F, for soprano, flute, and piano.
    Marx, Karl, 1897-1985. Music in two movements, flute, op. 53.
    Rosenthal, Herbert. Small divertimento, winds.
    Maderna, Bruno. Nocturne, tape.
    Maderna, Bruno. Syntaxis.
    Maderna, Bruno. Serenades, no. 3.
    Nono, Luigi. Epitaffio per Federico García Lorca, no. 2. Severino Gazzelloni, flute. Orchestra Alessandro Scarlatti di Napoli. Hermann Scherchen, conductor.
    Palmer, Robert, 1915-2010. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 2. Walden String Quartet (Urbana, Ill.).
    Palmer, Robert, 1915-2010. Trios, piano, violin, cello. Cornell University Trio.
    Bartók, Béla, ǂd 1881-1945. Volkslieder. Wiener Kammerchor.
    Poser, Hans, 1917-1970; Bresgen, Cesar, 1913-1988; Marx, Karl, 1897-1985; Maderna, Bruno; Nono, Luigi; Rosenthal, Herbert; Palmer, Robert, 1915-2010; Gazzelloni, Severino; Orchestra Alessandro Scarlatti di Napoli; Scherchen, Hermann, 1891-1966; Walden String Quartet (Urbana, Ill.); Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945; Wiener Kammerchor
  - Martinu: Fantasia concertante; Dallapiccola: Piccola musica notturno; Badings: Symphony no. 6, circa 1960-1961; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 219)
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959. Fantasia concertante. Margrit Weber, piano. Boston Symphony Orchestra. Charles Munch, conductor. 1st American performance. 1960-1961 season.
    Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1904-1975. Piccola musica notturna.
    Badings, Henk, 1907-1987. Symphonies, no. 6. Netherlands Radio Philhamonic Orchestra and Chorus. Willem van Otterloo, conductor.
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959; Weber, Margrit; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Munch, Charles, 1891-1968; Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1904-1975; Badings, Henk, 1907-1987; Radio Filharmonisch Orkest Holland; Radio Filharmonisch Orkest Holland. Koor; Otterloo, Willem van
  - Eshpai; Tormis; Melikov; Prokofiev; Stravinsky, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 220)
    Ėshpaĭ, A. (Andreĭ). Concerto for orchestra. Produced by Radio Moscow.
    Tormis, Veljo. Choral suite. Produced by Radio Moscow.
    Melikov, Arif, 1933-, Legenda o li︠u︡bvi (Legend of love, ballet suite). Produced by Radio Moscow.
    Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 5, op. 55, G major. John Browning, piano. Concertgebouw Orchestra of Amsterdam. Erich Leinsdorf, conductor.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Chant du rossignol (Symphonic poem). Concertgebouw Orchestra of Amsterdam. Erich Leinsdorf, conductor.
    Ėshpaĭ, A (Andreĭ); Tormis, Veljo, 1930-; Moskovskoe Radio; Melikov, Arif, 1933-; Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953; Browning, John, 1933-2003; Concertgebouworkest; Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971
  - Phibbs; Poulenc; Albeniz; Ibert; Stockhausen; Mahler; Ginastera, circa 1972; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 8, Reel 221)
    Phibbs, Milton. Music for brass and percussion. KKHI broadcast.
    Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Concertos, pianos (2), orchestra, D minor. Daphne Child and Linda Child, pianos. KKHI broadcast.
    Albéniz, Isaac, 1860-1909. Iberia. Fête-Dieu à Séville.
    Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962. Escales.
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007. Aus den sieben Tagen. From KPFA tape.
    Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphonies, no. 8, E♭ major. Final scene, Goethe's Faust. Deborah O'Brien, Linda Phillips, Jane Bryden, Susan Clickner, Eunice Alberts, John Alexander, William Dooley, Ara Berberian, soloists. Tanglewood Festival Chorus and Choir. Joh Oliver, director. Saint Paul's School Boy Choir. Theodore Marier, director. Berj Zamkochian, organ. Boston Symphony Orchestra. Seiji Ozawa, conductor. Final concert at Tanglewood. 1972.
    Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983. Concertos, harp, orchestra, op. 25.
    Phibbs, Milton; Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963; Albéniz, Isaac, 1860-1909; Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962; Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007; Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911; Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Ozawa, Seiji, 1935-; Tanglewood Festival Chorus
  - McPhee: Balinese music to accompany book 'Music in Bali', reel 1, circa 1928-1966; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 222)
    McPhee, Colin, 1900-1964. Balinese music, to accompany the book 'Music in Bali'. Recorded from 78 rpm discs dated 1928.
    McPhee, Colin, 1900-1964
  - McPhee: Balinese music to accompany book 'Music in Bali', reel 2, circa 1928-1966; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 223)
  - John Alden Carpenter, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 224)
    Carpenter, John Alden. unidentified works.
    Carpenter, John Alden, 1876-1951
  - Bruce Prince-Joseph, harpsichord, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 225)
    Bruce Prince-Joseph, harpsichord.
    Prince-Joseph, Bruce, 1925-2015
  - Pettersson; Back; Egge; Prinz; Leeuw; Hemel, circa 1971; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 226)
    Pettersson, Allan, 1911-1980. Symphonies, no. 7. Stockholm Philharmonic. Antal Dorati, conductor.
    Bäck, Sven-Erik. Tranfjädrarna, excerpts from the opera. conducted by the composer.
    Egge, Klaus, 1906-1979. Sonatas, piano, no. 2, op. 27. Kjell Martin Bækkelund, piano. LP dubbing.
    Prinz, Alfred. Symphonies, no. 4. San Francisco Symphony Orchestra. Josef Krips, conductor. World premiere. March 5, 1971.
    Leeuw, Ton de, 1926-1996. Symphonies, wind instruments. Hilversum Radio Philharmonic. Ernest Bour, conductor.
    Hemel, Oscar van, 1892-1981. Symphonies, no. 4. Hague Philharmonic. Willem van Otterloo.
    Pettersson, Allan, 1911-1980; Bäck, Sven-Erik; Egge, Klaus, 1906-1979; Prinz, Alfred; Leeuw, Ton de, 1926-1996; Hemel, Oscar van, 1892-1981; Konsertföreningens orkester (Stockholm, Sweden); Dorati, Antal; Bækkelund, Kjell Martin, 1930-2004; San Francisco Symphony Orchestra; Krips, Josef; Radio Filharmonisch Orkest (Nederlandse Radio-Unie); Bour, Ernest; Residentie-Orkest (Hague, Netherlands); Otterloo, Willem van
  - Makarova: Symphony; Busoni: Suite from 'Turandot'; Alfven: Symphony no. 4 in C, circa 1971; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 227)
    Makarova, Nina, 1908-1976. Symphony, D minor.
    Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924. Turandot (Incidental music). Suite. Hungarian State Radio Orchestra. Mario Rossi, conductor. October 9, 1971.
    Alfvén, Hugo, 1872-1960. Symphonies, no. 4, op. 39, C minor. Gunilla Af Malmborg, soprano. Sven Erik Vikström, tenor. Stockholm Philharmonic Orchestra. Nils Grevillius, conductor. LP dubbing.
    Alfvén, Hugo, 1872-1960; Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924; Makarova, Nina, 1908-1976; Magyar Rádió és Televízió Szimfonikus Zenekara; Rossi, Mario, 1902-1992; Konsertföreningens orkester (Stockholm, Sweden); Malmborg, Gunilla af, 1933-; Vikström, Sven-Erik, 1927-; Grevillius, Nils
  - Brian: Gothic symphony; Blomdahl: In the Hall of Mirrors; Lindegren: Poems of 1940, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 228)
    Brian, Havergal, 1876-1972. Gothic. Last movement only. BBC Symphony Orchestra. London Philharmonic Orchestra. Unnamed chorus and soloists. Adrian Boult, conductor.
    Blomdahl, Karl-Birger, 1916-1968. I speglarnas sal. Stockholm Philharmonic Orchestra. Sixten Ehrling, conductor.
    Lindegren, Erik, 1910-1968. Poems of 1940. The man without a way.
    Ehrling, Sixten; Boult, Adrian, 1889-1983; London Philharmonic Orchestra; BBC Symphony Orchestra; Konsertföreningens orkester (Stockholm, Sweden); Blomdahl, Karl-Birger, 1916-1968; Brian, Havergal, 1876-1972; Lindegren, Erik, 1910-1968
  - Japanese music: Lectures by Bob Garfias, reel 1, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 229)
    Japanese music. Lectures by Bob Garfias. Reel 1. Gagaku. Kagura. Soto no uta.
  - Japanese music: Concert at Los Angeles County Museum, 1958-02-16; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 230)
    Japanese music. Concert at Los Angeles County Museum. February 16, 1958.
    Los Angeles County Museum
  - Chinese music: Professor Ho-Ming Chung. KPFA, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 231)
    Chinese music. Professor Ho-Ming Chung, San Francisco. KPFA.
    KPFA (Radio station: Berkeley, Calif.); Ho, Ming Chung
  - Garfias: History of the Koto; Matsudaira: Orbites for flute, clarinet and piano, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 232)
    Garfias, Robert. History of the Koto.
    Matsudaira, Yoriaki. Orbites for flute, clarinet, and piano.
    Garfias, Robert; Matsudaira, Yoriaki
  - Japanese music: Utai, Okyo, Shakuhachi, Shamisen, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 233)
    Japanese music. Utai, Okyo, Shakuhachi, and Shamisen. Robert Garfias, lecturer.
  - Old Polish music; Serocki; Baird; Bach; Peter; Paderewski, circa 1968; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 234)
    Old Polish music. Program 2.
    Serocki, Kazimierz. Symphonies, no.1.
    Serocki, Kazimierz. Sinfonietta, string orchestra.
    Serocki, Kazimierz. Freski symfoniczne.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Eseje.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Sonety miłosne.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Wariacje bez tematu.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Sinfonia skrócie. Premiere performance. Rotterdam Philharmonic Orcestra. Hiroyuki Iwaki, conductor. Holland Festival. June 19, 1968.
    Bach, Wilhelm Friedemann, 1710-1784. Symphonies, F. 64, D major. Thuringian Chamber Orchestra of Weimar. Friedemann Batzel, conductor.
    Peter, Herbert, 1926-2010. Music for string orchestra. Thuringian Chamber Orchestra of Weimar. Friedemann Batzel, conductor.
    Paderewski memorial.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981; Peter, Herbert, 1926-2010; Serocki, Kazimierz; Bach, Wilhelm Friedemann, 1710-1784; Rotterdams Philharmonisch Orkest; Iwaki, Hiroyuki; Thüringisches Kammerorchester Weimar; Bätzel, Friedemann
  - Japanese Music: Demonstration of koto playing by Bob Garfias. KPFA, 1958-09-13; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 235)
    Demonstration of koto playing by Bob Garfias. End of Part 8 (Samisen) and start of Part 9 (History of the Koto). From KPFA tape. Recorded, September 13, 1958.
  - Original Dixieland Jass Band, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 236)
    Original Dixieland Jass Band. LP dubbing. RCA LPV 547.
  - Christoph: Rags, Cataract in B flat, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 237)
    Christoph. Rags. Save and copy all bits of 'Cataract' (Bb) to try to make a complete performance.
  - Walter Gerwig, lute; Bach: French overture, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 238)
    Walter Gerwig, lute.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. French overture [unspecified].
    Gerwig, Walter; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750
  - Delden; Prokofiev; Ridout; Jolivet; Berio; Poulenc, circa 1950; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 239)
    Delden, Lex van. Concertos, string orchestras (2), op. 71.
    Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 1, op. 10, D♭ major. Sviastoslav Richter, piano. Czech Philharmonic Orchestra.